RBRL/082/GGA
Richard B. Russell Library for Political Research and Studies
- II. Press Relations/Media Activities, 1983-2005; 3.0 boxes; (3 linear feet)
  - B. Press Releases, 1983-2003; 531 folders and 6 electronic files
    - Tax Administration. Betty Aaron – Ways and Means, January 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 109)
    - Mike Snow, January 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 110)
    - Media Memo – Radio, January 4, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 111)
    - Boyd Pettit, January 4, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 112)
    - Helen Selman, January 21, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 113)
    - Buddy Childers, January 21, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 114)
    - Eleanor Richardson, January 25, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 115)
    - Workman, Ken – Bill Toy Guns, February 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 116)
    - Bobby Lawson, February 4, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 117)
    - Larry Walker, February 10, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 118)
    - Larry Walker, February 18, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 119)
    - Ward Edwards, March 2, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 120)
    - Boyd Pettit, March 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 121)
    - Bob Peters, March 16, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 122)
    - Bob Peters, March 23, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 123)
    - [Buddy Childers, April 11, 1988] (Box II.1, Folder 124)
    - Buddy Childers, April 25, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 125)
    - Roger Byrd, April 29, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 126)
    - Tommy Smith, May 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 127)
    - Tom Lawrence, May 25, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 128)
    - James Moore, June 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 129)
    - John White, June 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 130)
    - Troy Athon, June 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 131)
    - Fred Aiken, June 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 132)
    - Bill Dover, June 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 133)
    - George Brown, June 3, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 134)
    - Troy Athon, June 14, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 135)
    - Bill Dover, June 28, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 136)
    - Hanson Carter, July 14, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 137)
    - Betty Jo Williams, August 29, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 138)
    - Betty Jo Williams, September 9, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 139)
    - Dick Lane, September 13, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 140)
    - Criminal Justice Albany Meeting, September 19, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 141)
    - Betty Jo Williams Eleanor Richardson, September 19, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 142)
    - Media Advisory Jimmy Lord, September 21, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 143)
    - Dick Lane, September 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 144)
    - Eleanor Richardson and Betty Jo Williams, September 30, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 145)
    - Property Tax Exempt Ion - Dick Lane, [October 12, 1988] (Box II.1, Folder 146)
    - Homestead Exemption Hearing, October 17, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 147)
    - Mike Barnett, Radon Gas, October 21, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 148)
    - Greensboro – Workshop George Hooks, October 21, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 149)
    - Wesley Dunn, October 24, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 150)
    - Wesley Dunn, November 1, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 151)
    - Eleanor Richardson, November 4, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 152)
    - [Wesley Dunn, November 8, 1988] (Box II.1, Folder 153)
    - Walter Quality Hearing Gainesville, November 29, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 154)
    - Committee Appointments, December 1, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 155)
    - Jimmy Lord, [December 1, 1988] (Box II.1, Folder 156)
    - Bill Dover, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 157)
    - [Dick Lane, December 5, 1988] (Box II.1, Folder 158)
    - Bill Cummings, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 159)
    - Tom Kilgore, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 160)
    - Bob Patten, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 161)
    - Bob Hanner, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 162)
    - Jimmy Benefield, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 163)
    - Bob Holmes, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 164)
    - Terry Coleman, December 5, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 165)
    - DeWayne Hamilton, December 6, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 166)
    - Barbara Couch, December 6, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 167)
    - Media Advisory – Cathey Steinberg, [circa 1988] (Box II.1, Folder 168)
    - Roy Allen, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 169)
    - Ward Edwards, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 170)
    - George Hooks, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 171)
    - Newt Hudson, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 172)
    - Bob Lane, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 173)
    - Jim Martin, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 174)
    - Clinton Oliver, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 175)
    - Charles Walker, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 176)
    - Betty Jo Williams, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 177)
    - Fulton County Public Hearing, December 8, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 178)
    - Wade Milam, December 9, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 179)
    - Bill Barnett, December 12, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 180)
    - Charlie Watts, December 15, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 181)
    - Dean Alford, December 19, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 182)
    - Roger Byrd, December 19, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 183)
    - Election of Officers – Fulton Delegation, December 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 184)
    - Lundsford Moody, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 185)
    - Ed Holcomb, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 186)
    - Max Davis, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 187)
    - John Godbee, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 188)
    - Bill Dover, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 189)
    - Bill Hasty, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 190)
    - Forrest McKelvey, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 191)
    - Nookie Meadows, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 192)
    - Wade Milam, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 193)
    - Frank Redding, December 20 ,1988 (Box II.1, Folder 194)
    - Howard Rainey, December 20, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 195)
    - Tom Crosby, December 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 196)
    - Mike Padgett, December 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 197)
    - Bubba McDonald, December 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 198)
    - Tom Buck, December 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 199)
    - Tommy Chambless, December 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 200)
    - Henry Reaves, December 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 201)
    - Bob Haner, December 27, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 202)
    - James Beck, December 28, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 203)
    - Bill Mangum, December 28, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 204)
    - Carlton Colwell, December 28, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 205)
    - Media Memo to Radio Stations, January 3, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 206)
    - Wesley Dunn, January 3, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 207)
    - [Butch Parish, January 3, 1989] (Box II.1, Folder 208)
    - Roy Allen, January 12, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 209)
    - Wesley Dunn, January 17, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 210)
    - [George Hooks, February 16, 1989] (Box II.1, Folder 211)
    - Phil Foster Speech, March 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 212)
    - Eleanor Richardson, February 24, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 213)
    - Eleanor Richardson, March 3, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 214)
    - Ralph Twiggs, March 3, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 215)
    - Eleanor Richardson Tax Deferral bill for Elderly, March 6, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 216)
    - House Position on Sales Tax, March 6, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 217)
    - Senate Rejects House Half Cent Sales Tax Proposal, March 7, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 218)
    - James E. McKinney, March 13, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 219)
    - Richard Royal, April 6, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 220)
    - Eleanor Richardson, April 11, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 221)
    - Tommy Smith, April 7, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 222)
    - DeWayne Hamilton, April 20, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 223)
    - Crawford Ware, April 24, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 224)
    - Wesley Dunn, April 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 225)
    - Ed Ricketson, April 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 226)
    - Goover Lucas, April 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 227)
    - Milam Moultrie, Ware. West Point Lake Study Committee, May 3, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 228)
    - Denny Dobbs, May 4, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 229)
    - Phil Foster, May 4, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 230)
    - Ron Fennel St. Simons Island, May 6, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 231)
    - Ralph Balkcom, May 6, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 232)
    - Emory Bargeron, May 6, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 233)
    - Tommy Smith, May 10, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 234)
    - Boyd Pettit, May 11, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 235)
    - Ken Poston, May 11, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 236)
    - Tom Buck, May 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 237)
    - Bill Lee, May 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 238)
    - Terry Coleman, May 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 239)
    - Larry Walker, May 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 240)
    - Frank Pinkston, May 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 241)
    - Jerry Jackson, May 25, 1989 (Box II.1, Folder 242)
    - Lauren McDonald, May 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 1)
    - Jack Connell, May 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 2)
    - Bob Holmes, May 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 3)
    - Barbara Couch, May 30, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 4)
    - Dick Lane, May 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 5)
    - Gerald Greene, May 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 6)
    - James Moore, May 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 7)
    - Suzi Johnson-Herbert, May 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 8)
    - Troy Athon-Bill Mangum, June 1, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 9)
    - Ken Poston, June 1, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 10)
    - Paul Heard, June 1, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 11)
    - Jerry Jackson, May 9, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 12)
    - Bobby Harris, June 12, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 13)
    - Bill Barnett, June 13, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 14)
    - Henry Bostick, June 13, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 15)
    - Dubose Porter, June 13, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 16)
    - Clay Davis, June 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 17)
    - Dick Lane, June 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 18)
    - Mike Barnett, June 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 19)
    - Jack Kingston, June 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 20)
    - Tom Crosby, June 15, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 21)
    - Hanson Carter, June 15, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 22)
    - Charles Thomas, June 16, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 23)
    - Buddy Childers, June 20, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 24)
    - Speaker Thomas Murphy, June 23, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 25)
    - Bill Lee, June 23, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 26)
    - Charles Yeargin, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 27)
    - William Dover, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 28)
    - Paul Smith, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 29)
    - Ron Fennel, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 30)
    - Mike Snow, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 31)
    - Nookie Meadows, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 32)
    - Paul Heard, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 33)
    - Henry Bostick, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 34)
    - Bill Cummings, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 35)
    - Ken Birdsong, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 36)
    - Media Advisory Frank Redding, June 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 37)
    - Johnny Floyd, July 5, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 38)
    - Tom Kilgore, July 5, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 39)
    - Grace Davis, July 6, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 40)
    - Barbara Couch, July 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 41)
    - Dick Lane Public Hearing, July 18, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 42)
    - Bill Dover, July 19, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 43)
    - Helen Selman, July 20, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 44)
    - Speaker Thomas Murphy Full Scale Drug Attack, July 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 45)
    - Eleanor Richardson, July 28, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 46)
    - Troy Athon, July 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 47)
    - Tom Buck, July 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 48)
    - Jack Connell, July 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 49)
    - George Hooks, July 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 50)
    - Eleanor Richardson, July 31, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 51)
    - Bill Barnett, August 2, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 52)
    - Tom Kilgore, August 3, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 53)
    - Buddy Childers, August 3, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 54)
    - Tommy Chambless, August 3, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 55)
    - Richard Royal, August 11, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 56)
    - Media Advisory – Dick Lane Discipline in Schools, August 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 57)
    - Mary Margaret Oliver, August 16, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 58)
    - Media Advisory – Dick Lane Public Hearing Columbus, August 18, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 59)
    - Richard Royal, August 18, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 60)
    - Bill Barnett, August 21, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 61)
    - Bill Dover, August 23, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 62)
    - Larry Smith, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 63)
    - Tommy Smith, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 64)
    - Mike Snow, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 65)
    - Lawton Stephens, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 66)
    - Deal Alford, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 67)
    - Wesley Dunn, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 68)
    - Forest McKelvey, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 69)
    - Billy McKinney, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 70)
    - Tommy Tolbert, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 71)
    - Frank Redding, August 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 72)
    - Roy Allen, August 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 73)
    - Roger Byrd, August 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 74)
    - Tom Kilgore, August 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 75)
    - Willou Smith, August 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 76)
    - Sonny Watson, August 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 77)
    - News Feed Letter Special Session, September 6, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 78)
    - Van Streat, September 7, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 79)
    - Bill Barnett, September 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 80)
    - Dick Lane, September 15, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 81)
    - Media Advisory – Nan Orrock Public Hearing – Savannah, September 26, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 82)
    - Tommy Smith Youth Subcommittee, October 10, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 83)
    - Media Advisory – Public School by Choice Public Hearing, Gainesville, October 13, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 84)
    - Radon Study Committee – Public Hearing, October 23, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 85)
    - E. Richardson Reward, October 24, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 86)
    - Richard Royal, October 25, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 87)
    - Dick Lane School Discipline Study Committee, October 26, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 88)
    - Joint House Education University System Postsecondary Proprietary School Interim Study Committee, October 26, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 89)
    - Public Hearing Movie Industry Hearing, October 27, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 90)
    - Bill Mangum, November 6, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 91)
    - Media Advisory-Medical Leave Hearing, November 6, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 92)
    - Special Drug Offender/Tax Enforcement Subcommittee, November 8, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 93)
    - Tax Hearing-Tifton, November 15, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 94)
    - Dick Lane, November 20, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 95)
    - Thomas B. Murphy Georgia Military Scholarship Act, November 30, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 96)
    - Roy Allen-Movie Industry Hearing, November 30, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 97)
    - Media Advisory Bill Mangum-Public Hearing-Savannah, December 6, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 98)
    - Cable TV Hearing, December 14, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 99)
    - Wesley Dunn, December 15, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 100)
    - Bill Barnett, December 15, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 101)
    - Wesley Dunn, December 21, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 102)
    - Atlanta Visitors Convention Bureau, December 28, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 103)
    - Bill Dover, December 29, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 104)
    - Frank Redding-Public Hearing, December 29, 1989 (Box II.2, Folder 105)
    - Tom Campbell, January 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 106)
    - Jerry Jackson, April 11, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 107)
    - Jim Martin, April 12, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 108)
    - Ward Edwards, April 19, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 109)
    - Jim Martin, April 19, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 110)
    - Tommy Smith, April 20, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 111)
    - DeWayne Hamilton, April 24, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 112)
    - Billy McKinney, May 14, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 113)
    - Betty Clark, May 14, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 114)
    - Charles Thomas, May 17, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 115)
    - Tommy Smith, May 22, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 116)
    - Jerry Jackson, June 6, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 117)
    - Bill Dover, June 15, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 118)
    - Jim Martin, June 15, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 119)
    - Forrest McKevley, June 15, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 120)
    - Van Streat, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 121)
    - Ken Birdsong, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 122)
    - Sonny Dixon, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 123)
    - Paul Heard, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 124)
    - LaNett Stanley, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 125)
    - Hanson Carter, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 126)
    - Bob Patten, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 127)
    - Jimmy Floyd, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 128)
    - Ken Poston, June 21, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 129)
    - Dobbs-Edwards, June 26, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 130)
    - Jim Martin, July 2, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 131)
    - Lawton Stephens, July 2, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 132)
    - Dubose Porter, July 2, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 133)
    - Mike Thurmond, July 18, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 134)
    - Helen Selman, July 18, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 135)
    - Mary Margaret Oliver, July 18, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 136)
    - Deal Alford, July 26, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 137)
    - Frank Pinkston, David Lucas, Denmark Grover, July 26, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 138)
    - Denny Dobbs, July 26, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 139)
    - Crawford Ware, August 2, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 140)
    - Roy Allen, August 2, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 141)
    - Roger Byrd, August 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 142)
    - Tom Kilgore, August 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 143)
    - Willow Smith, August 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 144)
    - Sonny Watson, August 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 145)
    - Frank Redding, August 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 146)
    - Dick Lane, August 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 147)
    - Bob Holmes, August 7, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 148)
    - Charles Thomas, August 15, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 149)
    - Tommy Smith, August 30, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 150)
    - Ken Birdsong Transportation Needs Study Committee, September 25, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 151)
    - Public Hearing Transportation Needs of Elderly, October 18, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 152)
    - Bill Dover, October 19, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 153)
    - Jim Griffin, October 19, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 154)
    - Ralph D. Abernathy III, October 23, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 155)
    - Committee Chairman Appointments, November 27, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 156)
    - Terry Coleman, November 27, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 157)
    - John Godbee, November 29, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 158)
    - Lawton Stephens, November 29, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 159)
    - Roger Byrd, November 30, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 160)
    - Butch Parrish, December 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 161)
    - Paul Heard, December 3, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 162)
    - Larry Smith, December 12, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 163)
    - Ralph Twiggs, December 26, 1990 (Box II.2, Folder 164)
    - Betty Jo Williams, January 4, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 165)
    - Anthony Hightower, January 7, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 166)
    - House Democratic Leadership Conference, January 17, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 167)
    - Media Advisory-Henrietta Canty, February 1, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 168)
    - Debra Mills, March 1, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 169)
    - Ralph David Abernathy, March 21, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 170)
    - Reappointment Hearings, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 171)
    - Maloof Center Decatur 7 pm, April 29, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 172)
    - Unicoi Park – Helen 7 pm, April 30, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 173)
    - Hamilton-Children Youth Study Committee, July 24, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 174)
    - Reaves-Disaster Aid, July 25, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 175)
    - Congressional Reapportionment Hearing, August 14, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 176)
    - Reapportionment Plan Adopted, September 9, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 177)
    - Betty Jo Williams, September 24, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 178)
    - DeWayne Hamilton, September 24, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 179)
    - [Workers Comp Hearing, October 18, 1991] (Box II.2, Folder 180)
    - [Workers Comp Hearing, October 24, 1991] (Box II.2, Folder 181)
    - [Workers Comp Hearing, November 5, 1991] (Box II.2, Folder 182)
    - Dunn INS Chairman, [November 16, 1991] (Box II.2, Folder 183)
    - [Workers Comp Hearing, November 18, 1991] (Box II.2, Folder 184)
    - Ralph Twiggs, December 16, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 185)
    - Bobby Lawson, January 6, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 186)
    - Bill Cummings, January 6, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 187)
    - Jimmy Skipper, February 21, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 188)
    - Grace Davis, March 27, 1991 (Box II.2, Folder 189)
    - Dorothy Pelote, April 14, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 190)
    - Bill Dover, May 29, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 191)
    - Tom Kilgore, July 7, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 192)
    - Willow Smith, July 13, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 193)
    - Larry Smith, July 28, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 194)
    - Bob Holmes, August 5, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 195)
    - Committee Chairman Named, December 18, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 196)
    - Butch Parrish, December 22, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 197)
    - Larry Smith, December 22, 1992 (Box II.2, Folder 198)
    - Van Streat, January 7, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 199)
    - Tommy Smith, January 11, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 200)
    - Larry Smith, January 20, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 201)
    - Mike Padgett, February 20, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 202)
    - Tommy Smith, January 29, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 203)
    - Ralph Johnson, February 2, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 204)
    - Hinson Mosley, February 4, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 205)
    - Ralph Johnson, March 9, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 206)
    - Bill Dover, April 13, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 207)
    - Bob Hanner, May 25, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 208)
    - Hinson Mosley, May 27, 1993 (Box II.2, Folder 209)
    - Bob Lane, January 28, 1994 (Box II.2, Folder 210)
    - Barbara Mobley, January 31, 1994 (Box II.2, Folder 211)
    - Bob Holmes, March 7, 1994 (Box II.2, Folder 212)
    - Henry Bostick, [undated] (Box II.2, Folder 213)
    - Hanson Carter, [undated] (Box II.2, Folder 214)
    - Committee Appointments, January 9, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 215)
    - Johnny Floyd, January 11, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 216)
    - Bill Cummings, January 24, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 217)
    - Mike Snow, January 26, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 218)
    - Newt Hudson, January 26, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 219)
    - Gail Buckner, January 26, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 220)
    - John Godbee, January 26, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 221)
    - [Harry Dixon, January 27, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 222)
    - [Ralph Twiggs, January 27, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 223)
    - [Butch Parrish, January 27, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 224)
    - [Sonny Watson, January 27, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 225)
    - [DuBose Porter, January 27, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 226)
    - [Bob Lane, January 27, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 227)
    - [Bob Haner, January 27, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 228)
    - [Tommy Chambless, January 31, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 229)
    - LaNett Stanley, January 31, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 230)
    - [Carolyn Hugley, February 1, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 231)
    - Ann Purcell, February 1, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 232)
    - Bob Holmes, February 2, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 233)
    - Jim Woods, February 3, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 234)
    - Gail Buckner, February 3, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 235)
    - Jimmy Skipper, February 6, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 236)
    - Bob Holmes, February 7, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 237)
    - Stallings, Tracy, February 7, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 238)
    - Buddy Childers, February 10, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 239)
    - Eugene Tillman, February 13, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 240)
    - Kem Shipp, February 13, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 241)
    - Regina Thomas, [February 17, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 242)
    - Tommy Smith, February 17, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 243)
    - John White, February 17, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 244)
    - Ralph Johnston, February 20, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 245)
    - Bob Holmes, February 22, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 246)